Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      - S
        - Simplicious - Let her feel it, 1984; SR-30232; Simplicious (Box 432)
          Philly World Records
        - Simply Jeff - Pacific breaks connection EP#1, 2000; SR-23027; Simply Jeff; Neosoul; Mizota (Box 432)
          Catalog # pm-003; A-side Matrix # S-44292 Re-1 SIMON THE EXCHANGE
          Phonomental Music
          Newport Beach, California
        - Simply Jeff - Funkengruven; Heart of Berlin, 2001; SR-30233; Simply Jeff (Box 432)
          Catalog # ELR-001; A-side Matrix # ELR 001 A1 S-46427 SIMON THE EXCHANGE
          Electro Life Records
        - Simply Jeff - Funk-da-fried trip; 21st century beats, 1999; SR-30234; Simply Jeff (Box 432)
          Catalog # pm-001; A-side Matrix # PRIMEDV S-42682 L-52492 X
        - Simply Jeff - Funk-da-fried trip; 21st century beats, 1999; SR-30235; Simply Jeff (Box 432)
        - Simply Jeff - Pacific breaks connection presents…, 2001; SR-30236; Simply Jeff; B-Side (Box 432)
          Title on discogs not song title
          Catalog # PM-005; A-side Matrix # PM-005 A S-46421 Sh@ne "Heathmans"
        - Simply Jeff - Funktastic boombastic EP, 2000; SR-30237; Simply Jeff (Box 432)
          In same jacket as # SR-30238. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PM-002; A-side Matrix # PM-002-A1 A PORKY PRIME CUT S-43270 L-52814
        - Simply Jeff - Funktastic boombastic EP, 2000; SR-30238; Simply Jeff (Box 432)
          In same jacket as # SR-30237. 2 copies.
        - Speed Freeks - Brutal B-boy; Shutdown (Mixes), 1999; SR-30239; Speed Freeks; Simply Jeff; Reverb, Kelly (Box 432)
          Catalog # JR 004; A-side Matrix # 9902XOJ A A+R SP61D Kelly Reverb
          Juice Recordings
          San Diego, California
        - Simply Jeff - Left hook remixes 98, 1998; SR-30240; Simply Jeff; Bassbin Twins; Mental Blox (Box 432)
          Catalog # OT-005; A-side Matrix # OT-005-A L-50034
          Orbit Transmission Records
          California
        - Simply Red - It’s only love, 1989; SR-30241; Simply Red (Box 432)
          Catalog # ED 5358; A-side Matrix # ST-ED 5358A 4 1-1 SFLATL
        - Simply Red - Remembering the first time (disc one), 1996; SR-30242; Simply Red (Box 432)
          In same jacket as # SR-30243. Double album.
          Catalog # ED 5841; A-side Matrix # ST ED-5841-A-1 F/W RCE
        - Simply Red - Remembering the first time (disc two), 1996; SR-30243; Simply Red (Box 432)
          In same jacket as # SR-30242. Double album.
          Catalog # ED 5841; A-side Matrix # ST ED-5841-C-1
        - Simply Red - A new flame, 1989; SR-30244; Simply Red (Box 432)
          Catalog # WX242; A-side Matrix # R/S Alsdorf 244689-1-A3 244689-A3
        - Simply Red - Picture book, 1985; SR-30245; Simply Red (Box 433)
          Catalog # 60452-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E-60452-A-1 1-3 Sf/atl
        - Simply Red - Money$ too tight (to mention) (The cutback mix), 1985; SR-30246; Simply Red (Box 433)
          Catalog # ED 5088; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66883-A 2 1-1 Sf/atl
        - Simply Red - Maybe someday…, 1987; SR-30247; Simply Red (Box 433)
          Catalog # ED 5247; A-side Matrix # ST-ED -5247-A-1 1-1 Sf
        - Simpson, James - On the money (Bounce-get down), 1980; SR-30248; Simpson, James; James Simpson Band Penetration (Box 433)
          Catalog # PNT-12001; A-side Matrix # PNT-12001-A S.J.S. FW HP
          Penco Records
          Garden City Park, New York
        - Simpsons - Do the Bartman, 1990; SR-30249; Simpsons (Box 433)
          Catalog # PRO-A-4179; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-4179-A-SR2
        - Sims, Joyce - All and all (The U.K. re-mix), 1986; SR-30250; Sims, Joyce (Box 433)
          Catalog # SLX-0020; A-side Matrix # SLX-0020 "THE BATTLE CONTINUES" MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
          Sleeping Bag Records
        - Sims, Joyce - Lifetime love, 1987; SR-30251; Sims, Joyce (Box 433)
          Catalog # SLX-0024; A-side Matrix # SLX-0024-X EDP NIL SFI SMI MASTERDISK DMM Howie Rules !!!
        - Sims, Joyce - Walkaway - the UK remix, 1987; SR-30252; Sims, Joyce (Box 433)
          Catalog # SLX-40136; A-side Matrix # SLX-40136 X F/W HERbIE Jr
        - Sims, Joyce - (You are my) All and all, 1986; SR-30253; Sims, Joyce (Box 433)
          Catalog # SLX-17; A-side Matrix # SLX-0017XA F/W
        - Sin/S.I.N. (Strength In Numbers) - Good time, 1990; SR-30254; Sin; S.I.N. (Strength In Numbers); Barry, Claudja (Box 433)
          Catalog # HAL 12191; A-side Matrix # HAL-12191-A FULLERSOUND RF
          Radikal Records
          Teaneck, New Jersey
        - Sinceros - Disappearing, 1981; SR-30255; Sinceros (Box 433)
          Catalog # AS 970; A-side Matrix # XSM168612-1G COLUMBIA NY
        - Sindecut - Changing the scenery, 1990; SR-30256; Sindecut (Box 433)
          Catalog # V 2635; A-side Matrix # V 2635 A-1U-1- D
        - Sindecut - Simple jealousy, 1991; SR-30257; Sindecut; Push (Box 433)
          Catalog # VST 1375; A-side Matrix # VST 1375 A -1U -1-1 D TOWN HOUSE DMM
        - Sindecut - Tell me why, 1990; SR-30258; Sindecut (Box 433)
          Catalog # VST 1288; A-side Matrix # VST 1288 A-1U-1-2 D
        - Sindecut - Won't change, 1991; SR-30259; Sindecut (Box 433)
          Catalog # VSTDJ 1326; A-side Matrix # VST 1326 A-1U-1- D TOWN HOUSE DMM
        - Sindecut - Angel of mercy, 2004; SR-30260; Sindecut (Box 433)
          Catalog # SDT001; A-side Matrix # SDT 001 A FU**** RIGHTEOUS
          Reference Library
        - Singing Dianne - Youth man, 1981; SR-30261; Singing Dianne (Box 433)
          Catalog # CRL 1016; A-side Matrix # CRL-1016A FW
        - Singing Francine - Keep the action going, 1979; SR-30262; Singing Francine (Box 433)
          Catalog # FCR 36; A-side Matrix # FCR-36-BB
        - Singing M.C. Breeze - Damn I'm good, 1988; SR-30263; Singing M.C. Breeze; DJ Trevor (Box 433)
          Catalog # BWAY 465 DJ; A-side Matrix # BWAY 465 A STERLING
        - Singing M.C. Breeze - Another sad song, 1986; SR-30264; Singing M.C. Breeze; DJ Hand Master Flash (Box 433)
          Catalog # DM-86007; A-side Matrix # DM-86007-A
          Breeze Records
        - Singleton, Charlie - Nothing ventured-nothing gained, 1987; SR-30265; Singleton, Charlie; Modern Man (Box 433)
          In same jacket as # SR-30266. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 49 07465; A-side Matrix # XSS-176287-1A G1 E STERLING
        - Singleton, Charlie - Nothing ventured-nothing gained, 1987; SR-30266; Singleton, Charlie; Modern Man (Box 433)
          In same jacket as # SR-30265. 2 copies.
        - Singleton, Charlie - I wanna boogie with you, 1981; SR-30267; Singleton, Charlie; Stargasm; Darnell, Rick; Stewart, Sam (Box 433)
          Catalog # DK 102; A-side Matrix # DK-102-A-1 PRC STERLING
          Dakar Records
        - Singleton, Charlie - Man on a mission, 1989; SR-30268; Singleton, Charlie (Box 433)
          Catalog # E 44320; A-side Matrix # AL-44320-3A G2 SKINNER EUROPA DISK A4
        - Singleton, Charlie - Nothing ventured-nothing gained, 1987; SR-30269; Singleton, Charlie; Modern Man (Box 433)
          Catalog # E 40939; A-side Matrix # AL-40939-1A DMM G1 B3
        - Sinister - I won’t forget you G, 1994; SR-30270; Sinister (Box 433)
          Catalog # DMD 2115; A-side Matrix # STDM-72511-72512-1 1-1
          Inerscope Records
        - Sinistr, Joe - Under the sun, 1994; SR-30271; Sinistr, Joe; Terminator X; The Godfathers of Threatt (Box 433)
          Catalog # 853-229-1; A-side Matrix # 853-229-1-A HUB TV MASTERDISK TD
        - Sinistr, Joe - Under the sun, 1994; SR-30272; Sinistr, Joe; Terminator X; The Godfathers of Threatt (Box 433)
        - Sinitta - Feels like the first time, 1987; SR-30273; Sinitta (Box 433)
          Catalog # DMD-1014; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-51171-1 1-1 ATLANTIC STUDIOS D. K.
          Omni Records
        - Sinitta - Cruising, 1984; SR-30274; Sinitta (Box 433)
          Catalog # SPV 87; A-side Matrix # SPV 87 A MASTERDISK BK P AP
          Vanguard
        - Sinitta - Cross my broken heart, 1988; SR-30275; Sinitta (Box 433)
          Catalog # DMD 1196; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-55114-1 1-1 ATLANTIC STUDIOS D. K.
        - Sinnamon - When I think of you, 1994; SR-30276; Sinnamon; Fowler, Barbara (Box 433)
          Catalog # ZYX 6697-12; A-side Matrix # ZYX 6697-12 A SST
          ZYX Music
          West Babylon, New York
        - Sinnamon - Say it again, 1986; SR-30277; Sinnamon; Jones, Brenda (Box 433)
          Catalog # SPR 12-420; A-side Matrix # SPR 12420 A-1 PRC MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK
        - Siouxsie & The Banshees - Dear Prudence; Dazzle (Edit), 1983; SR-30278; Siouxsie & The Banshees (Box 433)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2114; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2114-SH1 B-19368-SH1 SLM 6767 1-1
        - Siouxsie & The Banshees - This wheel's on fire, 1987; SR-30279; Siouxsie & The Banshees (Box 433)
          Catalog # 0-20609; A-side Matrix # 0-20609A SH1 B-26438-Re1-SH1 15398 1-1 Kdisc KP
        - Sir Elegance - Club world sweet house flavored beats & floor filling beats, 2001; SR-30280; Sir Elegance (Box 433)
          Catalog # CLBW-009; A-side Matrix # CLBW-009 A1
          Clubworld
        - Sir Fresh - I'm smooth, 1988; SR-30281; Sir Fresh; DJ Critical (Box 433)
          Catalog # MH 747; A-side Matrix # MH-747-A
          Solid Goals Records
        - Sir Ibu Of Divine Force - I'm the peacemaker; Ibu gets lyrical, 1989; SR-30282; Sir Ibu Of Divine Force (Box 433)
          In same jacket as # SR-30283. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BWAY 482; A-side Matrix # BWAY 482-A MASTERDISK
        - Sir Ibu Of Divine Force - I'm the peacemaker; Ibu gets lyrical, 1989; SR-30283; Sir Ibu Of Divine Force (Box 433)
          In same jacket as # SR-30282. 2 copies.
        - Sir Joe Quarterman & Free Soul - Sir Joe Quarterman & Free Soul, 1994; SR-30284; Sir Joe Quarterman & Free Soul (Box 433)
          Catalog # CPLP 8079; A-side Matrix # CPLP 8079 A DAMONT SIMON-THE EXCHANGE
          Chalry Groove
        - Sir Joe Quarterman & Free Soul - Sir Joe Quarterman & Free Soul, 1994; SR-30285; Sir Joe Quarterman & Free Soul (Box 433)
          In same jacket as # SR-30286. 2 copies.
        - Sir Joe Quarterman & Free Soul - Sir Joe Quarterman & Free Soul, 1994; SR-30286; Sir Joe Quarterman & Free Soul (Box 433)
          In same jacket as # SR-30285. 2 copies.
        - Sir Louie N' Prime - Get up and move…, 1990; SR-30287; Sir Louie N' Prime (Box 433)
          In same jacket as # SR-30288. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DNA-1007; A-side Matrix # DNA-1007-1A DMA cg
          DNA International Records
        - Sir Louie N' Prime - Get up and move…, 1990; SR-30288; Sir Louie N' Prime (Box 433)
          In same jacket as # SR-30287. 2 copies.
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - Mack daddy, 1992; SR-30289; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 433)
          Catalog # DEF 26765; A-side Matrix # 1-26765-A-SR1 DMM SP-1
          Def American Recordings
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - Square dance rap, 1986; SR-30290; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 433)
          Catalog # MKHAN 69 P2; A-side Matrix # MKHAN-69P-A2 DAMONT
          Streetwave
          London, United Kigdom
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - Ride, 1994; SR-30291; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 433)
          Catalog # 0-41693; A-side Matrix # 0-41693A SR1 1-
          American Recordings
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - Put 'em on the glass, 1994; SR-30292; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 433)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7075; A-side Matrix # PRO A1 7075-SR2
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - Square dance rap, 1986; SR-30293; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 433)
          Catalog # MKHAN 69; A-side Matrix # MKHAN-69P-A2 -1 DAMONT E
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - Sleepin' wit my fonk; I come buffalo, 1995; SR-30294; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 433)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7359; A-side Matrix # PRO A 7359 A SR2 1-1
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - Beepers, 1989; SR-30295; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 433)
          Catalog # NMR 76980-1; A-side Matrix # IGU-76980-1-A S-22573 G-1 MASTERED BY CAPITOL
          Nastymix Records
          Seattle, Washington
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - I just love my beat; Square dance rap, 1985; SR-30296; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 433)
          Catalog # IGU 6969; A-side Matrix # L10460 IGU-6969-A
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - Beepers, 1989; SR-30297; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 433)
          Catalog # IGU 76982-1; A-side Matrix # 76982-1-A Re-1 S-E1 S-22878-1
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - I'm a trip, 1986; SR-30298; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 433)
          Catalog # IGU 6970; A-side Matrix # IGU-6970-A S-6562 -RS-
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - Posse' on Broadway, 1988; SR-30299; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 433)
          Catalog # IGU 76974; A-side Matrix # IGU-76794-A S-20364 1 MASTERED BY EMI/A
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - I want a freak (Remix), 1987; SR-30300; Sir Mix-A-Lot; Kid Sensation (Box 433)
          Catalog # IGU 6971; A-side Matrix # S-17538 IGU-6971-A MASTERED BY EMI/A
        - Sir Mix-A-Lot - My hooptie, 1990; SR-30301; Sir Mix-A-Lot (Box 434)
          Catalog # IGU 76988-1; A-side Matrix # 76988-1-A S-23444 FUTURE DISC-T.B.
        - Sirenne, Gianni - Do whatcha wanna do, 1984; SR-30302; Sirenne, Gianni (Box 434)
          Catalog # DMD 787; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-46814-5 MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
        - Sirius B - If you technolectro, 2002; SR-30303; Sirius B; Afrika Bamabaataa; Hardy Hard (Box 434)
          Catalog # 74321 92370 1; A-side Matrix # B 258787-01 B1 MK
          Electric Kingdom
        - Sirius B - Tellievision, 2003; SR-30304; Sirius B (Box 434)
          test pressing; different jacket
          Catalog # 82876 57016 1; A-side Matrix # B380243-01 A1 HL
        - Sirius B - Tellievision, 2003; SR-30305; Sirius B; Afrika Bamabaataa; Hardy Hard (Box 434)
          Catalog # 82876 57016 1; A-side Matrix # B388515-01 A1 HL
          Low Spirit Recordings
        - Sirocalot - Sirocalot; Taking my stand, 1988; SR-30306; Sirocalot (Box 434)
          Catalog # RR-002; A-side Matrix # RR-002-A DCHARLES
          Ray Ray Recordings
          Queens, New York
        - Sisqo - Dance for me, 2001; SR-30307; Sisqo (Box 434)
          Catalog # DEFR 15341-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR 15341-1A
          Def Soul
        - Sisqo - Return of dragon (disc one), 2001; SR-30308; Sisqo; Dragon Family; Dru Hill (Box 434)
          In same jacket as # SR-30309. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 548 836-1; A-side Matrix # 314548845-1 A OASIS DISC ONE
        - Sisqo - Return of dragon (disc two), 2001; SR-30309; Sisqo; Associates; Chinky of Lovher (Box 434)
          In same jacket as # SR-30308. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 548 836-1; A-side Matrix # 314548846-1 A OASIS DISC TWO
        - Sisqo - Incomplete, 2000; SR-30310; Sisqo; MC Alistair (Box 434)
          Catalog # 572 754-1; A-side Matrix # 572-754-1+A JA 1-1
        - Sisqo - Can I live; Last night, 2001; SR-30311; Sisqo; LovHer (Box 434)
          Catalog # DEFR 15303-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR 15303-1 A 1 314572932-1-A
        - Sister Carol - Call mi Sister Carol, 1994; SR-30312; Sister Carol (Box 434)
          Catalog # HB 93; A-side Matrix # HB-93-A
          Heartbeat Records
          Cambridge, Massachusetts
        - Sister Carol - Liberation for Africa, 1983; SR-30313; Sister Carol (Box 434)
          Catalog # SG 8003; A-side Matrix # SG-8003-A 1e
          Serious Gold
        - Sister Charmaine - Body, 1988; SR-30314; Sister Charmaine (Box 434)
          Catalog # Tech Dis 001; A-side Matrix # TECH 005 A BODY 11 H
          Techniques
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Sister Charmaine - Charmaine de teacher, 1988; SR-30315; Sister Charmaine (Box 434)
          Catalog # Pick 03; A-side Matrix # PICK 03-A
          Pickout
        - Sister Charmaine - Fit ina body, 1988; SR-30316; Sister Charmaine (Box 434)
          Catalog # VPRD 350-A; A-side Matrix # CPRD-350-A SISTER CHARMAINE-FIT INA BODY- CS
          Steely & Clevie Records
        - Sister Charmaine - Charmaine de teacher, 1988; SR-30317; Sister Charmaine (Box 434)
        - Sister Charmaine - Shoot out clash, 1990; SR-30318; Sister Charmaine (Box 434)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # DSR A SIDE-575-SHOOT OUT CLASH-GEOVANNI TURNER-SIMPSON
          Las Records
          United states
        - Sister Charmaine - Watch the matie, 1988; SR-30319; Sister Charmaine (Box 434)
          Catalog # VPRD 351; A-side Matrix # VPRD-351-A WATCH THE MATIE-SISTER CHARMAINE CS
        - Sister Charmaine - Bun, 1991; SR-30320; Sister Charmaine (Box 434)
          Catalog # RN-001; A-side Matrix # RN-002-AA BUN - CHARMAINE VP-CM ROUGH NECK RAF
          Rough Neck Productions
        - Sister Mangie - Come fi mash mi down, 1988; SR-30321; Sister Mangie (Box 434)
          Catalog # TechDis 13; A-side Matrix # TECH-013-A TECH - Come fi mash mi -A- Kkmastering
        - Sister Nancy - Bam bam, 1993; SR-30322; Sister Nancy (Box 434)
          Catalog # 0-10113; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-64809-64810-1 F/M RCE
          Big Beat Reggae
        - Sister Power - Sister power, 1979; SR-30323; Sister Power (Box 434)
          Catalog # SW-49901; A-side Matrix # OR 49901 A-1A A6
          Ocean Ariola America
        - Sister Power - Gimme back my love affair, 1979; SR-30324; Sister Power (Box 434)
          Catalog # OR 7501; A-side Matrix # OR 7501 AS LONG RE1-1A A1
        - Sister Sledge - Got to love somebody, 1979; SR-30325; Sister Sledge (Box 434)
          Catalog # DSKO 212; A-side Matrix # ST-DK-37601-5 -2 ATLANTIC STUDIOS D.K.
        - Sister Sledge - He's the greatest dancer; We are family, 1978; SR-30326; Sister Sledge (Box 434)
          Catalog # DK 4710; A-side Matrix # ST-DKSKO-36222-2 (PR) ATLANTIC STUDIOS
        - Sister Sledge - Reach your peak, 1980; SR-30327; Sister Sledge (Box 434)
          Catalog # DMD 229; A-side Matrix # SRC ST-DM-38263-1 1-1 ATLANTIC STUDIOS D.K.
        - Sister Sledge - Frankie, 1985; SR-30328; Sister Sledge (Box 434)
          Catalog # DMD 850; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-47873-1 1-1 MASTERDISK
        - Sister Souljah - The final solution: Slavery's back in effect, 1991; SR-30329; Sister Souljah (Box 434)
          Catalog # 49 74071; A-side Matrix # XSS-74071A-1A G1 (T) A8 MASTERDISK
        - Sisters of Mercy - No time to cry, 1985; SR-30330; Sisters of Mercy (Box 434)
          Catalog # MR 335T; A-side Matrix # MR 335 T A//3 420V
          Merciful Release
        - Sisters of Mercy - This corrosion, 1987; SR-30331; Sisters of Mercy (Box 434)
          Catalog # 0-66790; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66790-A1 1-1 sf/atl
        - Size 9 - I'm ready, 1995; SR-30332; Size 9 (Box 434)
          In same jacket as # SR-30333. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 7243 8 38472 1 1; A-side Matrix # Y-38472-A-G1 1-1 "KEV" SP
          Ovum Recordings
        - Size 9 - I'm ready, 1995; SR-30333; Size 9 (Box 434)
          In same jacket as # SR-30332. 2 copies.
        - S.K - Gezzer style, 2003; SR-30334; S.K (Box 434)
          Catalog # SK001; A-side Matrix # SK001-A
        - S.K - Gezzer style, 2003; SR-30335; S.K (Box 434)
        - Skam - We didn't even need James, 1989; SR-30336; Skam (Box 434)
          Catalog # CR12033; A-side Matrix # CR-12-033 A F/W cg
          Criminal Records
        - Skatemaster Tate - Do the skate, 1991; SR-30337; Skatemaster Tate; Concrete Crew (Box 434)
          Catalog # 162-444 031-1; A-side Matrix # 162-444-031-1-A-SP 1-1
        - Skee-Lo - I wish, 1995; SR-30338; Skee-Lo (Box 434)
          Catalog # 72392 78032-1; A-side Matrix # SUN 12825-A S-30734
          Scotti Bros. Records
        - Skee-Lo - Top of the stairs, 1995; SR-30339; Skee-Lo (Box 434)
          Catalog # 72392 75486-2; A-side Matrix # 72392-78057-1-A F-1 S-32342 MASTERED BY CAPITOL Wally
        - Skee-Lo - Bounce back, 2001; SR-30340; Skee-Lo (Box 434)
          Catalog # S-48169; A-side Matrix # 6976-BOUNCE-1 S-48169
          Arphyltoine Music
        - Skee W. - Push, 1993; SR-30341; Skee W. (Box 434)
          Catalog # DBT-1119; A-side Matrix # DBT-1119 A
          Dance Baby Records
        - Skeewiff - Absent without leave EP, 1998; SR-30342; Skeewiff (Box 434)
          Catalog # FSUKT1; A-side Matrix # FSUKT 1 A-1-1-1 DIS A FOCKIN' RAID!! WALLY C-MASTERPIECE
          FSUK
        - Skeleton Rock - Three G.; Funkdafield, 1997; SR-30343; Skeleton Rock (Box 434)
          Catalog # Drum 018; A-side Matrix # DRUM-018-6-B
          Smokin' Drum
          Neckargemünd, Germany
        - Skibone - Take it to the top, 1986; SR-30344; Skibone; Ski, Tommy (Box 434)
          Catalog # TDE-3018; A-side Matrix # TDE-3018-A STERLING
          T.T.E.D. Records
        - Skibone - Take it to the top, 1986; SR-30345; Skibone; Ski, Tommy (Box 434)
        - Skinny Boys - Skinny & proud, 1987; SR-30346; Skinny Boys (Box 434)
          Catalog # 1078-1-JD; A-side Matrix # 1078-1-JD A CSB
        - Skinny Boys - Skinny & proud, 1987; SR-30347; Skinny Boys (Box 434)
        - Skinny Puppy - Dig it, 1986; SR-30348; Skinny Puppy (Box 434)
          Catalog # V-15267; A-side Matrix # V-1-15267-601221-A G-2 B-25823-G2 14761 1-1 MASTERED BY CAPITOL
        - Skinny Puppy - Chainsaw, 1987; SR-30349; Skinny Puppy (Box 434)
          Catalog # V-15281; A-side Matrix # V-1-15281-601218-A 601218B-G-2 B-26696-G2 15713 SP 0-1 AL-SP MASTERED BY CAPITOL
        - Skoog, Patrick - Foundation EP, 2000; SR-30350; Skoog, Patrick (Box 434)
          Catalog # NATIVE01; A-side Matrix # NATIVE01 A-1 MPO
          Native Diffusion
          Malmö, Sweden
        - Skoota - Let it out, 1996; SR-30351; Skoota (Box 434)
          Catalog # CRAB 12123-1; A-side Matrix # CRAB-12123-1-A1 RM
          Popular Records
          Winchester, Massachusetts
        - Skoota - Let it out, 1996; SR-30352; Skoota (Box 434)
        - Skrazzo, Stuart - Leaving England, 1986; SR-30353; Skrazzo, Stuart (Box 434)
          In same jacket as # SR-30354. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # TFW 1018; A-side Matrix # TFW 1018 AS F/W
        - Skrazzo, Stuart - Leaving England, 1986; SR-30354; Skrazzo, Stuart (Box 434)
          In same jacket as # SR-30353. 2 copies.
        - Skrein - Mind out; Once upon a skrein; The youth, 2004; SR-30355; Skrein (Box 434)
          Catalog # DNT 006; A-side Matrix # DNT006-A- - NAWEED DAMONT
          Dented
        - Skull Dugrey - Expression, 1996; SR-30356; Skull Dugrey; Skull Duggery (Box 435)
          Catalog # SPRO 30106; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30106-A S-34287
          New Orleans, Louisiana
        - Skunk Anansie - Stoosh, 1996; SR-30357; Skunk Anansie (Box 435)
          Catalog # TPLP85; A-side Matrix # TPLP 85 B DMM
          One Little Indian
        - Skunk Funk - Skunk funk, 2002; SR-30358; Skunk Funk (Box 435)
          In same jacket as # SR-30359. 2 copies. Annotated. No entry on Discogs
          Catalog # DSF2535; A-side Matrix # DSF2535-A
          Startime Entertainment Company
          Morningside, Maryland
        - Skunk Funk - Skunk funk, 2002; SR-30359; Skunk Funk (Box 435)
          In same jacket as # SR-30358. 2 copies. No entry on Discogs
        - Sky - Times like these; Do me, 1979; SR-30360; Sky (Box 435)
          Annotated. No entry on Discogs
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # FP-A MASTERDISK H.W.
          Copious Records
        - Skylite - Boogie butt, 1979; SR-30361; Skylite (Box 435)
          Catalog # 791; A-side Matrix # RPT-SS-7615
          Rampart Records
        - Skylite - Boogie butt, 1979; SR-30362; Skylite (Box 435)
          In same jacket as # SR-30363. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - Skylite - Boogie butt, 1979; SR-30363; Skylite (Box 435)
          In same jacket as # SR-30362. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - Skyywalker, Luke - Skyywalker's bass waves mega mixes, 1987; SR-30364; Skyywalker, Luke (Box 435)
          Catalog # GR-111; A-side Matrix # GR-111-A FULLERSOUND
          Luke Skyywalker Records